<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Debug</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="i">nVCiUUpuGyAm97rcA5jO7yR6FPEwTFPZGIiwuXYP</string>
    <string name="p">zd54zxmBPKrJUihd7vKQEmOm6UvlmmKUNdDtBcZS</string>
    <string name="title_activity_region_detail">RegionDetailActivity</string>

    <dimen name="detail_backdrop_height">256dp</dimen>
    <dimen name="card_margin">16dp</dimen>
    <dimen name="fab_margin">16dp</dimen>
    <dimen name="list_item_avatar_size">40dp</dimen>

    <string name="cheese_ipsum">Jarlsberg lancashire edam. Dolcelatte hard cheese brie st. agur blue
    cheese caerphilly bavarian bergkase cheese and biscuits mascarpone. Cheeseburger swiss bavarian
    bergkase cream cheese fromage frais cheesy feet port-salut airedale. St. agur blue cheese rubber
    cheese caerphilly cheddar cheesecake cream cheese manchego lancashire. Roquefort squirty cheese
    the big cheese.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_comparison">ComparisonActivity</string>

<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string name="info_pollutant_risks">What are the risks?</string>
    <string name="info_pollutant_risks_CO">In case of high concentrations, carbon monoxide can cause poisoning characterized by headache, nausea and vomiting. Carbon monoxide is particularly present and dangerous indoor because of some boilers and can lead to coma and death in case of prolonged exposure.</string>
    <string name="info_pollutant_risks_NO2">It is responsible for bronchitis and asthma especially in children and may also contribute to the decreasing of the lung function in case of high concentrations.</string>
    <string name="info_pollutant_risks_O3">Ozone might cause asthma, eye irritation and can lead to respiratory and heart diseases.</string>
    <string name="info_pollutant_risks_PM">Fine particles cause many nasal allergies. Chronic exposure to fine particles is a risk factor for cardiovascular and respiratory diseases and lung cancer.</string>
    <string name="info_pollutant_risks_SO2">SO₂ can irritate the skin and the respiratory tract. At high concentration it can even cause respiratory diseases and modify the lung defense mechanism.</string>
    <string name="info_pollutant_risks_VOC">They can cause irritations and a decrease of the breathing capacity in case of high concentration. Some VOCs are classified as carcinogenic.</string>


</resources>
